Lord Orochimaru gave us an important task
to take care of when we reach this point.
I'm afraid you're going to have to die
just this once.
I must die?
This once?
You will take one of these... awakening
pills.
And just what'll happen after that?
Not to worry, Sasuke.
Why do you think that we're all here?
We'll cast a barrier ninjutsu to minimize
the transition.
Instead of dying, you'll only be suspended
in a state of half-death.
One thing's for sure.
I can't afford to die.
Not yet.
All right, then.
Now!
Four Black Mists Formation!
And now, Black Seal!
There.
That'll hold him for now.
You're weak, Sasuke.
Damn it!
A little pause... and we are back.
I see.
You've made up your mind, then?
Yes.
I have already been carrying out fitness
training to prepare for the surgery.
I will return to action as soon as I can
after I heal.
Lee.
Yes, ma'am.
What is it?
You can quit as a shinobi.
It won't kill you, you know.
What is it with you?
Why are you so fixated on being a shinobi?
It is everything to me.
I must prove that with
enough heart, even
someone with my faults
can become a real ninja!
But it's important you realize.
There is still a chance that you could
die.
Even so.
That's a promise.
It is my dream.
What can I say?
Tell me.
What makes you so touchy about Hokage?
It's because unlike you, that's my goal!
Just watch, because someday I will be the
Hokage!
To be Hokage.
That is my dream!
Hmm.
Such ambitious children seem to come from
this world.
From this village.
Sarutobi-sensei, I can see you were a
magnificent Hokage.
The surgery is this afternoon.
You should prepare yourself.
Let's go, Lee.
Are you ready for this?
Yes, ma'am!
I'm exhausted.
Who would have ever guessed that this mission
would turn out to be such a tough one?
Shhhh.
Stay here while we check it out.
Raido, come on.
Right.
Great.
It looks like we've got company.
There's just one.
No, wait, two of them.
Get ready!
You've finally found your home!
You've found your home, and you know
you've got to go.
All right, then.
They work for Orochimaru.
And judging from the path
these four are taking, I guess
they've just come from the
village hidden in the leaves.
What you got in the coffin?
Fighting two Jonin at once?
I'm trembling at the prospect.
They all have curse marks.
You might want to think this over.
It won't be like last time when you jumped
us all by surprise.
Yeah, you're right, scum.
You won't survive this time.
Trust me, you pawns of Orochimaru.
You don't want to mess with the Leaf
Shinobi.
Where are they?
It's been too long.
So you think maybe something's happened to
them?
Let's go find out.
Right.
Akamaru?
What's the matter with him?
He smells blood.
Somewhere nearby.
What happened?
Aido!
Genma!
This isn't good.
All
I can do right now is just try and
stabilize him.
I'm going, Shizune.
I'm going to find them and make them pay.
No, you won't!
What?
What do you mean?
She's right, Iwashi.
They... they were using jutsu.
Beyond the powers of mere shinobi.
If you go after them, you'll only be
killed.
Genma, that's enough talking.
Here's what happened.
The scent of two newcomers converged on
the scent of Sasuke and four others.
The two have stayed behind while Sasuke's
group has moved on.
So what now?
Just as I thought.
Sasuke's got an escort.
Man, this is turning out to be such a
drag.
There's no question!
We gotta go after Sasuke!
Who died and made you boss?
Last time I checked, Shikamaru was in
charge of running this show.
It's up to him to decide.
Hmph!
Well, Shikamaru...
Since Akamaru smelled blood,
my guess is that there was
a battle between Sasuke's
group and the two newcomers.
If we go to the spot
where they fought, we
might be able to gather
some useful information.
Of course, we can't just rush in.
It might be a trap.
So when we get closer, we'll go into full
reconnaissance mode and take it slowly.
And while we're doing that,
Sasuke will have crossed beyond
the borders of the Land
of Fire and out of our hands.
Okay, Shikamaru, so what's it gonna be?
We follow Sasuke.
Way to go!
I knew you'd make the right choice!
One thing.
What?
These guys have already been in one fight,
so they'll be on their guard.
Unless they're complete
idiots, they'll have to
know there's gonna be
more ninja on their trail.
There's a good chance we'll hit some booby
traps or even an ambush up ahead.
So from this point on, we proceed with
caution.
I want everybody, not just Akamaru,
to put all your senses on full alert.
If you catch a trace of anything
suspicious, sound the alarm.
We want to find these guys before they
find us.
Ha!
Got it!
And when we do find him, I'm gonna clobber
him with this brand new jutsu of mine!
That Naruto.
Every time I turn around, he's got a new
trick up his sleeve.
And just when I thought I'd finally caught
up to that little pain in the neck...
The enemy's scent is here, all around us!
Everyone stop!
Look up on that tree.
See that?
A paper bomb.
I'm sure there's five more of them.
A perimeter barrier.
That's what it is.
A perimeter barrier?
It's a type of trap ninjutsu.
There's a delay after the perimeter is
breached, giving the victim just enough
time to get to the center of the area for
the full effect.
It's a tricky jutsu.
I learned about it in one of the books my
dad used to make me read.
Now we gotta waste time going around it.
Great.
Man, this whole forest is crawling with
booby traps.
Yeah, but luckily they're easy to spot.
These guys are moving fast and getting
sloppy.
Naruto, do me a favor and watch where
you're going.
I don't want you blowing us all up.
There's tripwires everywhere.
Tell me something I don't know!
Naruto, hold it!
Huh?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Just in time.
Got him.
With my shadow possession jutsu.
Didn't I tell you to watch your step,
you moron?
I get it.
One wire catches the light and is easy to
see, the other is camouflaged.
While you're busy avoiding the first,
you trip the second.
We've created a trap within a trap.
They're clever, whoever they are.
All their other traps were quick and
dirty, as if they were moving fast.
But not this one.
They may have stopped to rest.
Perhaps one of them is injured.
Or is this part of the trap?
Yakuza!
I see them.
Well, let's go!
I'm dying to show these clowns what I've
got!
Is that right?
Hate to disappoint you, hotshot, but I've
got a new jutsu I've been working on too.
Yeah, me too.
Alright, calm down.
First we make a plan and get everything
ready.
Then, we nail these bastards.
It drives me crazy.
Stopping and having to rest when we should
be moving on.
Buu, what did you expect?
You think you can fight a level 2 battle
without feeling the effects?
To feel like your whole body is completely
useless, it's frustrating.
Can't be helped if you're gonna take on
two Jonin-level ninja.
If we'd held anything back, we'd have been
dead.
That's it.
Now Kiba, the timing of those smoke bombs
is absolutely crucial, got it?
I got it.
So...
Split up.
Let's go.
Looks like we've caught him napping.
Hm?
Hold on.
Where's Sasuke?
He's in there.
Inside that coffin.
You don't mean he's dead?
It's been sealed with a barrier,
jutsu.
That's hard for me to see through clearly.
Considering they went through
all that trouble to get him,
I can't believe they'd be
willing to kill him so quickly.
Let's just hope you're right.
Well, well.
I thought I was flushing a snake out of the
bushes, but all I got was a couple of mice.
Wait a minute.
Calm down.
We're here to negotiate, not to fight.
Can't we talk this over like reasonable
people?
Heh.
Let's not forget your friends,
shall we?
Waaaaaah!
What good's that gonna do?
Throw all the smoke bombs you want.
I've still got you.
These threads are so fine, they're almost
invisible.
But they're stronger than they look.
You may have already encountered them in
the forest.
Darn it!
So that double trap of tripwires you said,
in fact, was actually a triple trap.
Heh.
That was clever.
So I guess that makes you the smart one of
the group.
You're about to be the dead one!
My body!
What's happening?
Man, that was perfect!
Keepin' distractin' him, and you nailed
him with your shadow-possessin' jutsu!
Yeah, that's right.
You're not the only ones who can spring a
trap.
Thanks for making me look good in front of
the squad.
Appreciate it.
Very impressive.
I'd be even more impressed if I hadn't
mastered that technique as well.
Huh?
What was that?
Earth-style barrier.
Earth Dome Prison!
Since I'm the one who caught him,
I get him.
Anyone else have a problem with that?
Heh.
Go ahead.
But we're not waitin'.
When you're done with them, catch up with
us.
Don't take all day.
Hey, you out there!
Let us out right now!
Yeah, like that's gonna help.
Cuddling bag!
The damn wall's rebuilding itself.
Hey, did you just-Yes, we saw it.
What is that?!
Yakugan!
The wall is... it's what?
The wall is what?
Our chakra!
It's absorbing it, as if it were a sponge.
Huh?
Great!
It's not enough they bury
us alive in this oversized
dung heap, now they're
trying to steal our chakra!
You gotta give these guys credit for
thoroughness, at least.
No way!
No way they can do this to us!
Whoever you are, let us out of here right
now!
I feel like all my energy is draining out
of me.
Something must be done, Shikamaru.
And quickly.
Man, I was an idiot to move in without
knowing the full extent of the enemy's powers.
Now we're trapped like rats.
That's... that does it.
Stand back, guys.
I'm gonna bust out of here before my
chakra's all gone.
Akamaru!
Have a food pill.
Okay.
Ninja art.
Human mimicry.
And as for me, ninja art beast mimicry.
Fang over Fang!
Attaboy, Kiba!
Go for it!
Go on.
Knock yourself out.
Look at that.
As soon as a crack appears, it repairs
itself.
Same with the ground beneath it.
I'd give us about ten more minutes of this...
before our chakra's completely drained.
And we're back.
No use.
I need all my energy to focus for the
Rasengan.
There's no way in here.
I've lost too much chakra as it is.
Hey, out there.
Let me talk to your leader.
I've got a deal to propose.
What I'm thinking is that you let us out
of this thing.
And in return, we let you keep Sasuke.
Huh?
But Chikamaru, what are you doing?
My favorite part.
When they start pleading for their life.
No deal.
I've never let a captive go before.
I'm not about to start now.
Aw, come on.
Listen, how about you just let me go and
keep the others?
All this fighting.
I'm tired of it.
It's really not my thing.
You little... If you're selling us
out... I'm gonna wring your neck!
Shut up, Kiba.
For once in your life.
What did you say?
So much for teamwork.
So you're really the leader, huh?
What a fine example you're setting for the
rest of your team.
You see a man's true character when he's
pushed to the edge of death.
But you're hardly a man at all.
Certainly not one who's worthy of leading
a team of ninja into battle.
Hmm.
Sacrificing Sasuke and the rest of your
squad.
Huh.
So that's how a Leaf Chunin acts.
Did you really believe I might let you
out?
You deserve to die.
That doesn't, Shikamaru, you dirty little
traitor!
Let's take this outside!
Just you and me!
What do you mean, take this outside?
How are you gonna do that, you idiot?
We're trapped in here.
What'd you call me?
I called you an idiot, idiot!
That's what I thought you said!
That's enough!
Everybody just shut up!
Huh?
Choji?
Neji, I need you to focus
those eyes of yours on the
wall directly behind you
and directly behind Choji.
Do you think you have enough chakra left
for that?
I think so.
Hold on!
You're not gonna listen to him!
Naruto!
You still don't get it, do you?
Don't you remember what Shikamaru said
when we came together as a team?
I know I usually seem like a pretty lazy
guy, but not today.
Because now I'm responsible for your
lives, too.
Okay, Choji.
Try and keep your voice down, will ya?
Kiba, are you up for trying to put another
dent in the wall behind Choji?
Well, sure.
I guess.
Hyaa!
Holy fang!
Huh.
Bleh!
Ugh.
Their Okay.
Now, Neji, mark the spot with your kunai
knife, will you?
Choji, are you ready, buddy?
Shikamaru, I was born ready.
Good.
Then let's get started.
Wait, let's get what started?
As I said a moment ago, this wall
surrounding us has been infused with chakra.
However, the strength of the chakra won't
be uniform.
Some points in the wall must be weaker
than others.
Shikamaru was able to figure that out.
He did?
Really?
You could have fooled me.
When the heck was this?
He's been watching, and taking it in.
For example, when Kiba and Akamaru
attacked the wall.
While you were watching them, he was
studying the wall.
And he observed that some areas repaired
themselves more slowly than others.
That led him to suspect that it was at those
points that the chakra was the weakest.
Still, he needed to be sure.
That's why he spoke to our captor as he
did.
It was a ruse, to trick him into giving
away his position.
And it worked, confirming that Shikamaru's
suspicions were right.
The band of chakra
running through the wall was
thinnest and weakest at the
point opposite his position.
That's about right, isn't it?
Hmph.
Heh.
And all the time, we thought he was
selling us out.
Gotta hand it to him.
He not only fooled the enemy, he had us
going, too.
It's up to you, Choji.
Okay!
Expanse in Jutsu!
Alright!
Here we go!
Baro!
Human Krogan!
Aaaaaaaaaaah!
Well, Choji.
..
There's no other way of
saying it... That was awesome!
heh heh heh heh!
Not a bad bit of handiwork, you guys.
We're a bunch of losers.
What?
Who are you calling losers?
Now that we're out, you're toast,
pal.
Out of the way!
This guy's mine!
Wait, you two, stop!
There's no way we can take him head on.
It's too dangerous.
We just tore through this clown's barrier.
How tough can he be?
Earth-style spear of gray!
Are you insane?
Haha, you're in charge of this ragtag
bunch, am I right?
When you've got an idiot for a leader,
the whole team suffers.
Know what I mean?
You don't want to follow a guy like this?
Let me get rid of him for you!
It's Batshit Chuchu!
Human form now!
Thanks, Choji.
Oh, I try to help you guys out and look
what you do.
I don't know which is more pathetic,
the fool or those who follow him.
Tell you what, you don't
want to keep working
under this glum-faced
little shadow lover.
I'll just kill you now and put you out of
your misery.
It's time for you to shut your big mouth,
or I'll come shut it for you!
Naruto!
I'll handle him.
This guy is mine.
Hmm?
Choji...
What the heck are you talking about?
This isn't the kind of guy you can take on
your own!
He's mine, I said!
Yeah, but... Choji, you're...
Shikamaru, take these food pills for
everyone.
Choji, you're not
gonna... Uh-huh.
Don't worry, I've got my secret weapon
with me.
Yeah, but Choji, this is...
Oh, this is priceless.
You think I'm gonna wait forever?
Enough!
Enough of this!
I'm taking you all out right here!
Get going!
Hurry!
Pills?
Those aren't food pills.
So what are they?
First, the green spinach pill.
Get out of my way, you joke!
Impossible!
He stopped me!
Shikamaru!
Take everybody and get out of here!
Choji... What did the five
of us join together for?
If we lose Sasuke, we'll be just what this
guy says we are!
A stupid idiot of a leader and his band of
rejects!
You'd better catch up with us,
Choji.
You hear me?
Yeah!
Get out of here!
Go already!
All right, let's move, you guys!
Right!
Choji... Once I finally finish you off
here, kid, your friends are gonna be next!
That might not be as easy as you think it
is!
Wait, wait, wait!
I'll make you pay for this!
I will... I will...
I'll stop you.
A parting gift from Choji.
Eat up.
Got it.
We owe you one, Choji.
Kiba!
Thanks, Naruto.
Shikamaru, that certain pill we saw Choji
take back there...
It seemed like some sort of last-minute
trump card.
Do you really think he can win?
Yeah, I mean, he said he had some sort of
secret weapon on him.
Don't worry, Choji's got a plan up his
sleeve.
He brought along with him the Aki Michi
clan's secret triple threat.
Pills that grant a person explosive power.
There are three of them.
Green, yellow, and red.
The amount of energy that each of those
pills contains is absolutely massive.
Oh, I gotcha!
So that's why he was acting so confident!
Yeah, but any pill that works that well
always comes with side effects.
I didn't think the spinach pill by itself
would hurt so much!
I hope he can settle things with the green
pill alone.
Just don't take the red one, Choji.
Whatever you do.
I'm gonna finish this all in one blow!
Hmm?
Hmm.
Expansion... CHO-CHO!
SPIKY HUMAN BOWLER!
AAAAAAAAH!
He's upped his rotation and destructive
power by using those kunai-like spikes.
AAAAAAAAH!
Earth-style Terra Shield!
What a shiii...
AAAAAAAAAAH!
AAAAAAAAH!
Don't get carried away, you little fool!
WHOO!
CHATTER... CHATTER... POW!
AAAAAAAAH!
Huh?
Huh!
No one ever told you?
In every team of five, there's always
somebody in the mix who's just dead weight.
The guy who's always the butt of
everyone's jokes.
And when thick comes to thin, he gets cast
aside like the worthless pawn he is.
That's who you are.
Look, Choji.
You've got to stop thinking about food.
Do some training for once.
Ridiculous stunts like this are why
everyone always makes fun of you.
You're such a fat.
But for this kind of
thing, don't you think
your first choice should
be someone like Shino?
No matter how hard I try on my own,
I...
I... Looks like I hit it right on the nose.
It looks as though the Leaf Village is
running short on ninja.
If they're sending out bunglers like you
to be part of a search team.
But...
Maybe they're just making fun of me.
Just a little of my time for the
not-so-good-for-me.
In this age, I'll let you do what you want
with even a little help.
Alright, let's go.
Let's go!
Well, I'm sorry, Shino.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
We'll take care of it some other time.
But I'm probably not as good a fighter as
you are.
I mean, really.
If I had been facing off against you,
I probably would have given up the fight.
And you should just keep being you.
But... Shikamaru, he's always... Huh?
Shikamaru, he's always believed in me.
Choji, are you ready, buddy?
He believes I really am strong.
That's why you trusted me to handle this
myself!
Pretty aggressive, Chuck.
Not bad.
But a far cry from being a main dish.
Here I come, Fatso!
Don't you call me that!
I'm not a fatso!
You're a fatso!
I'm a fatso!
Don't mess with me, scum!
Oh, this... What the...
Super Inferno Jutsu!
Shikamaru, I did it!
What?
I don't believe I have to go to the second
state for an opponent as weak as this one.
Slamming Pulse!
Super Inferno Jutsu!
What the... He changed his form!
I'm afraid it's all over for you.
In second state, I'm invincible.
I can dish out ten times as much power as
I could before.
It hurts to move.
I didn't know the side effects of a curry
pill would be so intense.
You better listen to me, because I'm about
to teach you an important lesson.
This is what happens to weaklings!
You're pathetic.
You'd be better off playing ninja with
your friends.
It's for Choji.
He promised us he'd catch up.
Trust me, he will beat that guy.
And after he does, he'll come and find us.
No doubt about it.
If anyone can defeat him, it's Choji.
Well, as long as we've stopped.
Good idea.
All right, everyone.
Let's go.
Let's get Sasuke back before Choji catches
up.
Huh?
Hey, wait for me!
All right!
Here we come!
Jirobo's late.
He should have gotten here by now.
Well, you know how enormous his appetite
can be.
He's probably squeezing out every last bit
of chakra.
Man, I wish I could be in his shoes right
now.
Huh?
Now that I'm in my second state,
I'm gonna need a lot more chakra.
Which means I'm going to have to take
whatever you have left inside you!
All right, kiddo.
Let's get this over with!
Huh?
You don't have very much left,
do ya?
Empty already?
Are you ready?
You weakling!
I'm still hungry!
I said, I'm still hungry!
Oh, of course.
Fatso only left one chip.
Well, I guess I'll take what I can get.
How does it feel to be a pawn?
To be sacrificed by your so-called
friends?
Left here for dead.
A pitiful Fatso.
The odd man out.
You can't play ninja with us anymore!
But why can't I?
Because whenever you play with us,
we lose.
Yeah, you're way too slow.
You know, guys, without him, the teams
aren't gonna be even.
It'd be lame, like if he played a game of
shogi with one piece missing.
Huh?
But if you have one piece that's totally
useless, it's the same thing.
Yeah, what he said.
It's our team, and we don't mind having
one less person, so let's just play.
Well, if it's okay with you, I guess it's
fine.
Okay then, it's settled!
We're so gonna win this time!
Yeah!
Where should we hide?
What do you think?
At least Chunky's not playing.
Here's the plan.
You guys go left, I'll take the right and
hide in the alley.
And they said the whole Akimichi clan is
fat and slow.
Then everybody laughed at me.
Did they really?
Let me tell you something, son.
None of those boys have as kind a heart as
you do.
Hmm?
And someday you'll have
a group of real friends who
see that quality inside
you and respect you for it.
You'll find friends who believe in you,
who trust you with their lives.
Cherish those friends, Choji.
I...
Huh?
Oh, it's you!
Hmm?
Oh, yeah.
You were with those kids.
Weren't you playing ninja with them?
Heh.
They were a drag, so I quit.
Really?
By the way, you're kinda sitting on my
special spot.
Your special spot?
Yeah.
On a nice day like this,
I always come out here
and lie on my back and
just stare at the clouds.
You know?
You came to look at clouds?
That's right.
So can I sit?
Oh, sure.
This is such an awesome spot.
The sky looks amazing.
You're right.
Hey.
What?
The clouds are pretty cool from down here.
Wanna lie back and watch with me?
Uh, yeah.
Thanks.
Hey, you know, I brought some snacks with
me.
You wanna share them?
That'd be great!
Hey, thanks.
Eating chips and watching clouds.
Man, this is the best.
Yep.
By the way, my name's Shikamaru.
I'm from the Nara clan.
What about you?
What's your name?
It's Choji.
My name is Choji, and I'm from the
Akimichi clan.
Choji, huh?
I got a feeling that you and me'll be
friends.
Yeah, me too.
Hmph.
Shikamaru, I'm sorry.
I'm not gonna catch up.
It's over.
Say your prayers.
No.
I have to stop him.
Even if it means I die, I've got to win.
There's nothing you can do to stop me!
P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-
Mm-hmm.
Sounds good.
Awesome.
Your mom probably thinks a lot of me like
that, doesn't it, Thot?
You think so, don't you?
Yeah!
Set, go!
Go!
C'mon!
Shikamaru, are you okay?
I'm okay.
A hundred times stronger than before.
People hold grudges when you take
something important from them.
Like, for instance, their food.
That strike I gave you was for eating the
last bite of my favorite snack.
Impossible.
This bug has so much chakra, his body's
actually changed.
And this next attack...
is for calling me names like Pawn,
Fatso, and Loser!
I can handle being picked on, but what
you've done is unforgivable!
He was my best friend, and you insulted
him!
How dare you!
You can steal my very last bite of my very
best food, you can mock me all you want,
but when you insult my best friend...
I will obliterate you!
All of my chakra... to my left hand!
This last attack... is worth my whole
life!
Please, no!
Please don't do it!
I did it!
A guy like me... I beat him!
My friends...
Oh...
What's the matter?
We're getting close!
That's strange.
It's been quite a long time and we still
haven't encountered a single trap.
Well Shikamaru, what's your assessment?
It looks to me like we've been
underestimated.
They're cocky.
They think we're all dead now, and their
big guy's the only one following them.
They don't need to set a trap for their
own man, do they?
Those idiots!
They think we're so weak!
It seems you're right about our enemies,
Shikamaru.
And it's insulting to be underestimated
like this.
But still, this could be our chance.
I hear ya.
Now we can take him by surprise.
Jirobo's pretty late, isn't he?
He was, but he just arrived.
Well, it's about time.
You were gone a while.
What took so long?
Sorry.
It took longer than I thought to eat all
that loser's chakra.
Listen, fatso.
Don't slow us down so you can eat more.
You see that coffin?
You're the one who's supposed to be
carrying it.
So do your job, you slob.
Okay.
Well, well, Jirobo.
Aren't you awfully easygoing today?
Yes, so what?
Well, it's just that I'm not going to be
handing over this coffin to you.
Because you're not the real Jirobo!
You're just gonna have to calm down for a
better chance.
Let me take down this one, fellas!
Sackon!
Tayuya!
Go on!
I'll catch ya!
The real Jirobo is always scolding Tayuya
about her rather coarse language.
I'm not a good kid to quiet down after
all.
Hmm... You got me.
Ninja Art!
Spider Web Net!
Surprise!
Did you see me?
Ninja Art!
Spiral Spider Web!
Fang Over Fang!
I won't let you get away!
You stole my line, punk.
You should look down at your feet.
You coward!
Do you really think you can stop us that
easily?
Why don't you shut up?
My turn.
Huh?
Nachi, no!
He's stuck!
Darn it.
He got me, Naruto, Kiba, and Nachi.
We followed the plan, but it's not
working.
Huh?
Aww...
I can't believe it.
How'd you like to see the inside of an
airtight cocoon?
No!
Come on!
What the heck's this thread made out of?
I can't cut it!
It's useless.
My spider silk is so powerful,
nothing can break it.
Two elephants couldn't pull it apart.
Heh, that one's able to use Shadow Clone.
No matter what I do, this thread keeps
sticking to me.
Finally.
This stickiness must come from combining
his chakra with some sort of fluid.
And the strength is unreal.
Even after he releases
the thread, his chakra
is still flowing through
it, giving it power.
Impossible!
The level of this jutsu is out of this
world!
It's unstoppable!
No, wait.
I've got to calm down.
Focus my chakra.
Ninja Art!
Sticky Spider Thread!
That's a different color from the thread
he used before.
What's he gonna do?
I see.
It's solidifying.
Since you'll be my first victim,
let's make this entertaining.
I'm going to play a little game to find
out which one of you is the real one.
What did you just say?
Contestant one, let's try you at the end.
Whichever you are, you're pretty lucky.
Next, let's try two at a time.
The odds will be doubled in my favor.
You are a very lucky guy, you know that?
But this time, I got a 50-50 shot.
Here it comes!
Well, somehow we made it all the way to
the bitter end.
Well, weakling, it was fun playing with
you.
But unfortunately, the game's over for you
now.
Now die!
One down and three to go.
Wait, where did he...
Of course, he let his shadow
clones get caught while the
real one hid and waited for a
chance to catch me off guard.
For a wimp like that to come up with such
a deception in the heat of battle.
He's not so dumb after all.
However...
It looks like you're at the end of your
rope.
How did he...
Naruto!
Thanks for stalling him for me.
Magi!
I trapped you.
How did you get free?
Ah!
Your spider web had a chakra base.
And chakra-built substances don't stand a
chance against my gentle fist attack.
This guy's jutsu.
I think I'm the only one who can handle
it.
Go on, you guys.
I'll take care of him.
We all embarked on
this mission to find
Sasuke and bring him
back home to the village.
But that's not the only reason that we've
come.
We are on this mission to protect a fellow
shinobi.
To defend the bond of the Hidden Leaf
Village.
Listen.
Sasuke's out there right now, heading
toward Orochimaru.
We can't allow such evil to take someone
from our village.
That is not our way.
What's more...
Naruto...
Sometimes your eyes are even better than
mine.
Wherever he is...
Sasuke is in the darkness.
Now, get going!
I'll be right behind you.
Well, all right.
Let's do this thing.
When you catch up with us, make sure you
bring Choji, too.
Of course I will.
Oh, no you don't!
Yakugan!
He's pretty good.
This is going to be fun.
Thanks, Neji!
Yep, that's him, all right.
Well, that's just fine by me.
Besides, you're by far the strongest one
of the lot.
Okay, the game is I'll kill you in three
minutes or less.
Yes.
You're not going anywhere.
For a wimp, you're pretty good at handling
chakra, aren't you?
And those eyes of yours are pretty sharp.
You fire off chakra from the chakra points
in your hands like a sharp needle.
Then you target the thin
part of my thread with
chakra running through
it and strike there.
Yes, I heard this from Lord Orochimaru.
It's the technique you call gentle fist,
right?
But if you can't use those
annoying hands of yours,
then you won't be able
to cut through my silk!
That was way too easy.
Once you figure out
your opponent's rules of
engagement, games like this
one are no longer amusing.
It's only been a minute or so.
And I'm already tired of playing with you.
Die!
How did he.
..?
I suppose you want me to explain how I
broke free.
You see, it's not just my hands.
There are chakra points all over me.
I can emit chakra from any one.
And now, as you would say, game over.
Gentle fist art.
Eight trigrams.
Sixty-four palms.
Two palms.
Four palms.
Eight palms.
Sixteen palms.
Thirteen palms.
Thirty-two palms.
Sixty-four palms.
Transient power art.
encryption
What's going on?
The surface of his body?
Ready.
It's the same material as that weapon he
spit from his mouth.
Well, well, that was close.
I know if I take just one
direct hit from that gentle
fist of yours, my whole chakra
network goes out of whack.
You keep me on my toes, kid.
That material... where does it come from,
you monster?
Impressive, yes?
My sticky spider thread
is actually a type of
metal that hardens the
instant it leaves my body.
It's impervious to chakra.
And what's more, not only
can I secrete it from my mouth
as you've seen, but from
every sweat gland in my body.
That explains it.
No wonder my attacks on his chakra points
have no effect.
The spider web net won't
work on him, and close range
combat is suicide against
that gentle fist of his.
I'll just have to keep my distance and
look for a blind spot.
The knife's just a ploy.
Eight trigrams... rotation!
What the?
Impossible!
He... he repaired it.
He repelled my attack with his chakra.
But how?
How did he see it coming?
Does he have eyes in the back of his head?
No way!
Can he actually see me?
What kind of a freak is this guy?
I know you're there.
Come out!
It's those eyes.
The chakra flow's not the only thing they
can see.
The power of his visual jutsu is beyond
belief.
Long-distance combat is not to my
advantage.
I've got to get closer to him somehow.
Okay, then.
I give you credit.
You've made this game more of a challenge
than I thought it would be.
Time to start playing for real.
He's like a totally different opponent.
His chakra activity's staggering.
And those markings...
So, this guy is able to see me in the
dark, and to dodge an attack from behind.
In other words, he's got 360-degree X-ray
vision.
On top of that, there's that jutsu.
All right.
Summoning jutsu!
If he can block the physical attacks by
emitting lots of chakra and rotating...
Then all I have to do is stop that
rotation.
Scatter!
Rotation!
There.
That slowed him down.
Now!
Now you die!
The jutsu has been activated.
He slowed my dagger with Chakra at the
last second!
What?
His web stopped my rotation!
Our Chakra cancelled each other out!
Enough of this!
If my rotation jutsu won't work, I'll
just have to cut the threads one by one!
His strength is close-range taijutsu, so
as long as I keep my distance, I'm alright.
Just keep pounding away at him.
I've got all the time in the world.
Allright.
Eight Trigrams, 64 Pounds!
There's no end to them!
Huh?
He changed his stance.
Eight trigrams?
One hundred twenty-eight bombs!
What?
The number of blows has doubled!
He gets the chance to use that on me,
and we've finished.
Well, if it's a numbers game, two can play
at that!
There's too many of them, and not enough
time!
Just as I thought!
The rotation won't work!
So that's how it is.
He's been anticipating my attacks by
combining his X-ray vision with telescopic
long-range vision, as well as a 360-degree
line of sight!
Add to all that his
lightning-fast reflexes, and this
kid's got an almost
impenetrable defensive barrier!
Judging from his reaction time during that
last attack, he's able to see and react to
the kunai knives once they get within
fifty meters of his position!
But not quite all...
Somehow or another, one of them got
through.
And that means... there's a blind spot!
Eight trigrams, sixty-Yeah,
just as I thought.
You saved the world, kid.
Seeing as it's the last ball, I'll try
again.
Hahahaha!
What is that?!
Now more!
Of course!
Go, go, go!
You can do it, kid.
Now, come on!
Two should get through!
Hahahaha!
Oh, nukes.
I told you I'd find a way around your
defenses.
Actually, right through your defenses.
All those fancy moves
of yours, they're all just
an attempt to hide your
blind spot, aren't they?
Those eyes don't quite see everything,
do they?
Am I supposed to be impressed?
Why bother?
The game's over!
You can't beat me!
Time to wrap this up.
It's probably just as easy to stop here or
to get out of this house.
I'm not really a genius, am I?
Here we go.
That's a pretty good start.
I'm glad we managed to get that.
Yeah...
I'm already...
I only need the two of you to help me out
here.
Here you go.
How do we do this?
I actually enjoyed myself, even though the
ending was predictable.
That
many hits from that distance, and he's
still standing?
I'll have to work out my aim.
This kid is something else.
He's turning out to be a lot more
entertaining than I ever dreamed.
I'll have to demonstrate my appreciation.
Striking accuracy!
100%!
Destructive power!
Maximum!
Die!
It's over.
What?
Just barely.
That was close.
But I was able to throw it off course a
little.
There's no mistake.
He's caught on to the secret of the
Byakugan.
What's going on here?
How did he...
What gives?
How could I miss it by 15 centimeters?
The See.
That chakra...
All this time, he's been releasing a steady
flow and surrounding himself with it.
In such a wide range, it's
no wonder he sends the
arrow coming, and was
able to throw off its trajectory.
Não tem como perder aärkeiro.
being at a distance all the time.
Chakram at level.
But if he doesn't keep it up, he won't be
able to dodge.
There's no doubt about it.
It's just as I thought.
My arrow was totally invisible to him.
He makes no pointless attacks.
He's been culling information with every
move.
And he's discovered the weakness behind my
eyes.
Impressive.
He's the strongest opponent I've ever
fought.
He has a blind spot
emanating from a small
point just behind the
first thoracic vertebra.
As long as he keeps
that blind spot moving,
it'll be hard to sling
an arrow down its path.
That's not enough to stop me.
The gentle fist is useless if you can't
get close to your enemy.
And you can't even think of approaching me
right now, in the state you're in.
All you can do is run.
It doesn't matter if you struggle or not.
Either way, you're gonna die!
It's useless.
A thread?
I see.
He's using it to...
The trajectory was thrown off by the
trees, huh?
I can still see the tree.
If that's the case, I'll add a little spin
this time.
Even if this one hits a tree, it'll slice
right through to find its target.
And just like the first time,
I'll spin a thread infused with
chakra to control the arrow
till it gets within his range.
Even if he's moving, I'll just pinpoint his
blind spot and plunge the arrow into it.
Still on your feet, huh?
He's strong.
Much stronger than I am.
I'm almost out of chakra.
I can't dodge another attack.
Is this it?
I vow to win!
Naruto, what would you do, I wonder?
He stopped moving.
Well, better safe than sorry.
Striking accuracy.
120% destructive power.
Absolute maximum!
Get him!
Got him!
So close!
Gentle fist!
What?
What the... He's still... No!
That last shot should have killed him!
And chakra-built substances don't stand a
chance against my...
Gentle Fist attack.
Gentle Fist, of course.
He funneled the last of his chakra through
the thread.
Eight crows.
And again, I couldn't see one of them.
He damaged several of my internal organs.
But... I can still move.
Unlike me, you're not a failure.
Well, boys, it looks like it's just the
three of us left now.
I don't think you have to worry about
that.
Choji and Neji are gonna catch up in no
time!
Choji's got his trump card with him.
And don't forget, I fought Neji in the
Chunin exam, so I know!
You know what?
That guy... is a true genius!
I cannot lose.
Even if my enemy is far stronger... Even
if my body should fail me... I cannot lose!
There is a reason I cannot lose!
I let it drag on!
I let it drag on too long.
I played too hard.
тест I stole her mortal skin.
I stole her mortal skin.
And they killed Simba.
I can't build up any chakra!
But how?
You should be dead!
Why are you still alive?
I couldn't have evaded it anyway.
So I decided to take the hit deliberately.
So you did it on purpose, huh?
Knowing you were gonna die here anyway.
Why would you go that far?
You are the strongest enemy I have ever
fought.
But there is a reason why I cannot lose.
Once, not so long ago, the strongest person
I ever fought out of everyone said to me...
You can do it too, cause after all,
unlike me, you're not a failure.
Those were his words.
All this time, I've been called a genius.
So I cannot lose.
I can't let down those who believe in me.
Go ahead, try all you want.
There's no way you can stop it.
It's too late.
Sasuke Uchiha has fled to the sound
village of his own free will.
No.
There is someone who can find him in the
darkness.
And save him from this path.
Sasuke belongs to Lord Orochimaru now.
I don't care who it is.
They can't save him.
He will!
Because... Naruto... It was you who saved
me from the darkness.
Dogging rubbish right up to the end.
I haven't been pushed this far since
Kimimaro.
Where did I go wrong?
Cause you...
You...
What?
That's impossible... I don't
know where this is going... This...
I'm not going to let go.
This is not going to happen.
Trample!
It's a job.
It's my job.
A little pause... and we are back.